{
    "subject": "resource/Benito_Caballero_Garza",
    "predicate": "ontology/ethnicity",
    "object": "resource/Mexicans",
    "human_readable": "Benito Caballero Garza is a Mexican.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9872766137123108,
            "question": "Is Benito Caballero Garza Mexican?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9845713376998901,
            "question": "Is Benito Caballero Garza from Mexico?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7114171385765076,
            "question": "What nationality is Benito Caballero Garza?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6973038911819458,
            "question": "Where is Benito Caballero Garza from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6655682325363159,
            "question": "What is Benito Caballero Garza's nationality?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6634798645973206,
            "question": "To which country does Benito Caballero Garza belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.642957329750061,
            "question": "Benito Caballero Garza's origin is in which country?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.594562292098999,
            "question": "What is the ethnicity of Benito Caballero Garza?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5432057976722717,
            "question": "From which nation does Benito Caballero Garza hail?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3799619972705841,
            "question": "Is Benito Caballero Garza's origin in Europe?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Benito Caballero Garza is a Mexican.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5146_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=From which nation does Benito Caballero Garza hail?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5146_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the ethnicity of Benito Caballero Garza?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5146_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Benito Caballero Garza's origin is in which country?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5146_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5146_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5146_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5146_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5146_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5146_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5146_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5146_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5146_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5146_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5146_57.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that Benito Caballero Garza is a Mexican politician, indicating he is indeed of Mexican nationality."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}